Ajay,
welcome to your own channel Market
Update. So today we will see about the dance done by ICICI
Lombard General Insurance Company along with the
added
details and also look at the fundamentals
and what is the position of the company.
ICICI Lombard General Insurance is the
best private sector mall in India.
Life insurance means it
comes from companies but
not life insurance, it is like two
wheeler insurance, four wheeler
insurance,
home insurance,
such as tyre shop, insurance will come from these words, so there is
a front company, the
company has recently digitalized it, we will
see its details
that it is from the fundamentals of the company and the
market capitalization of the company is Rs 7300 crores,
Rs 62 crores, this means this is the last
step company and the price of the company is
also running very expensive,
this stock is seen to be at an edge here and the
price to book value of the company is 9.9 or
almost times more than its value,
so I would suggest
not to invest in the stock for now,
wait a bit and then invest, but those who
already have this stock, you  You
can keep this stock folded, the company also gives dividend, the stock
of the company is above the family of seven two at 0.49
and the market price of the company
is more than 100, the face value of the company
is ₹10, it has a
very high chance of going ahead, so you
can invest in it for long term, further you will
see the wooden details, the cash withdrawal has been done in the company,
that is of equity shares
and for which a cigarette company has given 2
February
2014, the record date is 1
November 2011, so first of all if someone
wants this diff, then the last date for that
is 28th October 2018,
if you bought this share on 28th then only
you can get this diff, if you
already have these shares then you do
not need to do anything, you do not see, it will be
credited to your account, this was today's
video, in today's video we saw
about the diff of the company,
we
also saw the record of the company, so our
channel is like this  Like, share and do
n't forget to subscribe, thank you.